Joseph Stephen Cullinan Collection, 1895-1939
University of Houston Libraries
- Box List
  - Personal Correspondence: George W. Goethals, 1925-1928 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: Goethals Committee, 1928-1932 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Goethals Committee, 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, A-K, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, L-Z, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, A-E, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, F-L, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, M, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, N-R, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, S-Z, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Credit and Currency Correspondence: American Board of Trade, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Credit and Currency Correspondence, "Blazing a Trail," 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Credit and Currency Correspondence: "Factors Pertaining to Credit," 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Credit and Currency Correspondence: "More Money of More Tourism," 1930-1932 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Credit and Currency Correspondence: Post Dispatch Editorial, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Credit and Currency Correspondence: Trade Acceptance, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Credit and Currency Correspondence, Henry Woodhouse, 1931-1937 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Credit and Currency Clippings: American Board of Trade (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Credit and Currency: Newspaper Clippings Concerning Henry Woodhouse (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Credit and Currency Correspondence: Publications on Trade Acceptance (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Credit and Currency: Publications from Henry Woodhouse (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Credit and Currency: Miscellaneous Materials (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Credit and Currency: Miscellaneous Materials (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Wright Patman, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, C.A. Hawkins, 1932-1933 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, A-D, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, E-L, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, M-D, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, P-Z, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Credit and Currency Correspondence, Wright, Patman, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, A-C, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, D-F, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, G-H, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, I-O, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, P-Z, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Joe H. Eagle, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Liberty League, August - October, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Liberty League, November-December, 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Wright Patman, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Sound Money League, 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Credit and Currency: General Correspondence, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Wright Patman, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Liberty League, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Liberty League, 1936-1937 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Frank J. Silsbee, 1929-1932 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Frank J. Silsbee, 1934-1936 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, John Walsh, 1919-1931, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Political Correspondence, 1922 - January 1923 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, E.G. Senter, 1925-1928 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, E.G. Senter, 1933-1935 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Irving Fisher, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Irving Fisher, 1935-1937 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Concerning Callie Pride, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Concerning Callie Pride, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, National Committee to Uphold Continual Government (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Concerning Education, 1922-1927 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Concerning Communism, 1935-1937 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Christianity and Communism, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Broadsides Concerning Communism, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Repeal Associates (Prohibition), 1936-1937 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Tax Relief Association of California, 1923-1936 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Jeffersonian Democrats of Texas, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Houston Association/Houston Garden Project Conflict, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Repeal Associates/Association Against the Prohibition Amendment, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Repeal Associates/Association Against the Prohibition Amendment, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Repeal Associates (Prohibition), 1935 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - National Prohibition Women's Organization, Texas, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - National Prohibition Women's Organization, Texas, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - National Prohibition Women's Organization, Texas, 1932-1933 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Anti-Prohibition Activity, Feb. - July, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Anti-Prohibition Activity, August, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Anti-Prohibition Activity, September, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Anti-Prohibition Activity, October, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Anti-Prohibition Activity, November, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Anti-Prohibition Activity, December, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Anti-Prohibition Activity, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Undated Anti-Prohibition Material (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Ireland, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Ireland, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Ireland, Feb. - March, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Ireland, April - Dec., 1928 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Ireland, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Ireland, 1931-1934 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Ireland, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ireland, 1936-1937 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Committee For the Nation, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Texas Democratic "Landon-For-President" Club, May 1935 - May 1936 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Texas Democratic "Landon-For-President" Club, June 1-19, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Texas Democratic "Landon-For-President" Club, June 20-30, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Texas Democratic "Landon-For-President" Club, July 1-15, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Texas Democratic "Landon-For-President" Club, July 16-31, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Texas Democratic "Landon-For-President" Club, Aug. 1-15, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Texas Democratic "Landon-For-President" Club, Aug. 16-30, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Texas Democratic "Landon-For-President" Club, Sept. 1-15, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Texas Democratic "Landon-For-President" Club, Sept. 16-30, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Texas Democratic "Landon-For-President" Club, Oct. - Dec., 1936 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Emma R. Newsboys Association, 1914-1915 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Emma R. Newsboys Association, Jan-July, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Emma R. Newsboys Association, Aug. - Dec., 1916 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Emma R. Newsboys Association, 1917-1919, 1925, 1927-1929 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Emma R. Newsboys Association, 1931-1934,1937 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, American Museum of Natural History, 1924-1937 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Geographical and Historical Society, Nov. - Dec., 1930 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Houston Yacht Club, 1927-1932 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Congressional Country Club, 1927-1936 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, English-Speaking Union, 1930-1935 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Houston Club, 1928-1934 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Friendly Sons of St. Patrick, 1936-1937 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Houston Museum and Scientific Society (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Houston Riding and Polo club, 1926-1936 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Concerning National Elections, Dec., 1931 - Oct., 1932 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Concerning National Elections, Nov. - Dec., 1932 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Concerning National Elections, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Concerning National Elections, 1934-1935 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Concerning National Elections, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Concerning Texas Elections, 1934,1936 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Concerning James Farley's Visit to Houston, Sept. - Nov., 1933 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Clipping Concerning James Farley's Visit to Houston, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence Concerning Houston Elections, 1916, 1917, 1921, 1922, 1924-1928 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Concerning Houston Elections, 1929-1933, 1935-1936 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, National Democratic Club, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Southern Committee to Uphold the Constitution, 1935-1936 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, Jan. - April, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, May 1931 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, June 1931 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, July - Aug., 1931 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, Sept. - Oct., 1931 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, Nov. - Dec., 1931 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, January 1932 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, Feb. - April, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, May - June, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, July - Aug., 1932 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, Sept. - Dec., 1932 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, Jan. - March, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, April - July, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, August - Dec., 1934 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, Jan. - April, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, May - Sept., 1935 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, Oct. - Dec., 1935 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, American Taxpayers League, 1936-1937 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1914-1916 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, January - June, 1917 (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, January - June, 1917 (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, July - September, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, October - December, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, January - March, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, April - June, 1918 (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, April - June, 1918 (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, July - August 15, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, August 16 - December, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, January - May, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, June - December, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, January - June, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, July - December, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1931 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1936 (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1936 (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Cullinan's Shadyside Residence, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Houston Negro Hospital, 1923-25 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Houston Negro Hospital, January - May, 1926 (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Houston Negro Hospital, January - May, 1926 (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Houston Negro Hospital, 1927-1928 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Houston Negro Hospital, June - Dec., 1926 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Houston Negro Hospital, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Houston Negro Hospital, 1930-32 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Houston Negro Hospital, 1933 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Houston Negro Hospital, 1934-37 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Houston Negro Hospital, Nurses' Home, 1930-32 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, Jan. - June, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, July - Oct., 1929 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, Nov. - Dec., 1929 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, Dec. 1929-1930 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, January 1930 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, February 1930 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, March 1930 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, April - May, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, June, July, August, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, Sept. - Dec., 1930 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Concerning Engraving and Printing of Mt. Rushmore Stationery, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, Jan. - May, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, June - Dec., 1931 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Financial Records of Mt. Rushmore National Memorial Commission, 1932 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, 1933-34 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Concerning Mount Rushmore, 1935-36 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Financial Records of Mt. Rushmore National Memorial Commission, 1934-37 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Food Administration, 1917-22 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Food Administration, 1917-22 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Food Administration [Lever Bill], 1917-22 (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Food Administration [Lever Bill], 1917-22 (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Food Administration [clippings], 1917-22 (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Food Administration [clippings], 1917-22 (2 of2) (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Texas Centennial, 1934-35 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Texas Centennial, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Texas Centennial (clippings, etc,) (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Texas Centennial (clippings, etc.) (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Texas Drought Situation, 1917 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Texas Drought Situation, 1917 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Texas Drought Situation, 1917-18 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Texas Drought Situation, 1917-18 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Texas Drought Situation, 1917-18 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Security Trust Company; Fidelity Land Co.; Houston Ship Channel-Todd Shipyard Corp. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Houston Tidewater Terminal (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - San Leon Co. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Petroleum Building Co. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Dallas Petroleum Co. (balance sheets, production reports), 1930 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Federal Investment Co. (miscellaneous), 1918 (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Federal Investment Co. (miscellaneous), 1918 (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Federal Investment Co. (highways) (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Federal Investment Co. (highways) (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Dividends - Bonds - Interests, 1919-36 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Dividends - Bonds - Interests (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Dividends - Bonds - Interests (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Bills Receivable, 1914-24 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - McNutt Lease, Watkins Property (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Petroleum Refining Co. of Texas, etc. (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Petroleum Refining Co. of Texas, etc. (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Income Tax, 1913-19 (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Income Tax, 1913-19 (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Stocks (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1919-20 and 1921 (pt. 1) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1919-20 and 1921 (pt. 2) (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Income Tax (Suit) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Personal Mailing Lists (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Federal Income Tax - General (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Federal Income Taxes (inclusive), 1916-26 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1920-22 (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1920-22 (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1922-24 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1925 (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1925 (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1925-28 (1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1925-28 (2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1929-36 (1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1929-36 (2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Northside Belt Railway - I.C.C. Application Hearing, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Northside Belt Railway - I.C.C. Application, 1920 - June 1927 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Northside Belt Railway - I.C.C. Application, July 1927 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Northside Belt Railway Co. - I.C.C. Application, August 1927-31 (1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Northside Belt Railway Co. - I.C.C. Application, August 1927-31 (2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Northside Belt Railway - T & No Injunction Suit, 1925 (1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Northside Belt Railway - T & No Injunction Suit, 1925 (2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Northside Belt Railway - T & No Injunction Suit, 1925-58 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Condemnation Suit, 1925-59 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Right of Way, 1925-34 (1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Right of Way, 1925-34 (2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - San Jacinto Centennial Association (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Maya Corporation (pamphlet), May 7 - July 31, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Maya Corporation (pamphlet), August1, 1926 - January 14, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Food Administration (ARA), 1917-20 (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Food Administration (ARA), 1917-20 (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Food Administration (ARA), 1917-20 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Maya Corporation, 1925-28 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Alabama, JSC - Options, 1925-26 (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Alabama, JSC - Options, 1925-26 (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Alabama - St. Louis & Ala. Coal & Iron Syndicate, 1925-29 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Maya Corp. - Alabama Meetings and Conferences (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Maya Corporation - Banking and Financing (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Maya Corporation - Alabama - Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Maya Corp. - Alabama - Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Miscellaneous, 1926-28 (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Miscellaneous, 1926-28 (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Miscellaneous, 1929-35 (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Miscellaneous, 1929-35 (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Automobile Club of America and A.A.A., 1927-1931, 1933, 1935 - 1937 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, American Red Cross, 1918, 1921, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, American Academy of Political and Social Science, 1914, 1916-1920 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, American Academy of Political and Social Sciences, 1923, 1925-26, 1930, 1932-33 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, American Relief Administration Association, 1934-1937 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Business Historical Society, 1929-1932, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, American Forestry Association, 1920-1935 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, American Irish Historical Society, 1926-1937 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, C.R.B. Educational Foundation, 1935-1937 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Aero Club of America, 1916-1918 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Aero Club of America, 1919-1922 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Commission for Relief in Belgium, 1916-1918 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, American Institute of Mining and Metallurgical Engineers, 1920-1921, 1926-1933, 1935-1937 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, American Mining Congress, 1928-1935 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, American Remount Association, 1927, 1929, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, American Peace Society, 1930-1935 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, American Arbitration Association, 1928-1929 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Academy of Political Science, 1923-1937 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Mississippi Valley Association, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Mississippi Valley Association, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Federal Housing Administration, 1933-1934 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Federal Housing Administration, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Texas Employer' Insurance Association, February - August, 1913 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Texas Employer's Insurance Association, September - December, 1913 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Texas Employer's Insurance Association, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Texas Employer's Insurance Association, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Texas Employer's Insurance Association, 1916-1917 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Lincoln Memorial University, 1926-1932 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Uptown Club, 1927-1932 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Texas Academy of Science, 1936-1937 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Tejas Club, 1930-1936 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Texas Economic League, January - November, 1915 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Texas Economic League, December 1915 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Texas Economic League, January - February, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Texas Economic League, March 1916 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Texas Economic League, April 1916 (Box 26, Folder 8)